{"items": [{"question": "Pertaining to knowledge", "answer": "gnostic", "options": ["diagnosis", "agnostic", "prognosis", "gnostic"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Uncertain of all claims to knowledge", "answer": "agnostic", "options": ["monotheism", "agnostic", "diagnosis", "prognosis"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Identifying the nature or cause of some phenomenon", "answer": "diagnosis", "options": ["diagnosis", "monotheism", "polytheism", "prognosis"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A prediction about how something will develop", "answer": "prognosis", "options": ["pantheism", "prognosis", "monotheism", "polytheism"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Belief in a single God", "answer": "monotheism", "options": ["monotheism", "pantheism", "theology", "polytheism"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Belief in multiple Gods", "answer": "polytheism", "options": ["libidinous", "polytheism", "pantheism", "theology"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Belief in  all gods.", "answer": "pantheism", "options": ["pantheism", "theology", "libidinous", "lascivious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "study of divine things or religious truth", "answer": "theology", "options": ["lascivious", "lustful", "theology", "libidinous"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "full of sexual lust", "answer": "libidinous", "options": ["lascivious", "lustful", "libidinous", "prurient"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "inclined to lustfulness", "answer": "lascivious", "options": ["lustful", "lubricious", "prurient", "lascivious"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "instigated by lust", "answer": "lustful", "options": ["lewd", "lubricious", "lustful", "prurient"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "inclined to have lustful thoughts", "answer": "prurient", "options": ["prurient", "licentious", "lubricious", "lewd"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "arousing sexual desire", "answer": "lubricious", "options": ["lubricious", "lewd", "pruritic", "licentious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "inclined to lust", "answer": "lewd", "options": ["lewd", "pruritic", "hypochondria", "licentious"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "sexually unrestrained", "answer": "licentious", "options": ["pruritic", "licentious", "hypodermic", "hypochondria"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "itching", "answer": "pruritic", "options": ["hypotension", "pruritic", "hypochondria", "hypodermic"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Chronic and abnormal anxiety about imaginary symptoms and illness", "answer": "hypochondria", "options": ["hypochondria", "hypodermic", "hypotension", "hypertension"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "introduction of medicine under the skin", "answer": "hypodermic", "options": ["hypotension", "hypertension", "hypodermic", "hypercritical"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Abnormally low blood pressure", "answer": "hypotension", "options": ["hypercritical", "hypotension", "hypertension", "hyperacidity"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Abnormally high blood pressure", "answer": "hypertension", "options": ["hypercritical", "hypertension", "hyperactive", "hyperacidity"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Inclined to judge too severely", "answer": "hypercritical", "options": ["hypersensitive", "hyperactive", "hypercritical", "hyperacidity"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "excess acidity of the gastrointestinal tract, esp the stomach, producing a burning sensation", "answer": "hyperacidity", "options": ["hyperacidity", "gnostic", "hyperactive", "hypersensitive"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "More active than normal", "answer": "hyperactive", "options": ["gnostic", "hyperactive", "agnostic", "hypersensitive"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "having unduly vulnerable feelings", "answer": "hypersensitive", "options": ["gnostic", "hypersensitive", "diagnosis", "agnostic"], "answer_index": 2}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 31.txt", "total": 24}